#### Contact

Tehran - Elahiyeh +989125502517 (Mobile) dj1372@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/a-fathollahi (LinkedIn)

# Top Skills

**CATIA** 

Django

Python (Programming Language)

## Languages

Persian (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

#### Certifications

Develop web applications with Python and Django

CATIA - Advance

Java cource

android programing cource sport assistant

# amirhossein fathollahi

Industrial Designer at Eideh Negar Giti - Fuji Tehran

# Summary

Hi, my name is amirhossein fathollahi and I am an Industrial designer. I work in Eideh Negar Giti - Fuji company and meanwhile I work as freelancer to help you transform your idea into reality. Here, you will be able to learn more about the area of my expertise, as well as get to know me as a person. I like working with my clients in a friendly atmosphere and be productive as much as possible. Contact me if you wish and I'm happy to work with you!

# Experience

Eideh Negar Giti - Fuji Industrial Designer June 2020 - Present (2 years) Tehran, Iran

- 1- Industrial design and reverse engineering of escalators parts with CATIA
- 2- presenting realistic parts and devices made by keyshot

#### Freelance

Industrial Designer January 2017 - Present (5 years 5 months)

doing industrial design project synce 2017

Azaran Industrial Structures

Manufacturing, production and assembly of industrial parts and structures

January 2016 - December 2016 (1 year)

Tehran, Iran

welding, Electrode welding, CO2 gas cutting, assembly, bending, cnc

Tarbiat Modares University **Building Services Engineering** January 2015 - December 2015 (1 year)

**Tarbiat Modares University** 

**HVAC** 

# Education

Iran University of Science and Technology

Master's degree, MBA marketing managment · (2020 - 2022)

Shahid Beheshti University
Bachelor, Mechanical Engineering · (2012 - 2016)

### Nikan

High School Diploma, Mathematics and Physics · (2008 - 2012)